

PROFILE

My name is Charlie Freeman. I live in Smyrna, TN and have a eight year old son named Wyatt. I am looking for opportunities in which allow growth and continued development in a career field that better fits my personal interests. I enjoy learning new skills and applying them in my daily routine. In my free time I love puzzles, board games, social events, and playing sports or being outdoors with my son. In my professional life I am committed to achieving a standard that exceeds what is set by my employer. I continue to learn and improve on whatever it is I am currently working on.

CONTACT

Cell:

615-967-5004

Email:

Clfreeman22@gmail.com

Linked-In:

www.linkedin.com/in/clfreeman22

Portfolio:

Clfreeman22.com

CHARLES LEE FREEMAN III

General Manager

EDUCATION

Blackman High School 2004-2007 3.67 GPA

Varsity Baseball Beta Club National Honors Society

Robotics Team Math Team JROTC Rifle Team

Tennessee Tech 2007-2011 2.9 GPA

Mechanical Engineering

Member of Tau Kappa Epsilon Recruitment Chairman

Vanderbilt Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp Graduated in Feb 2022
HTML CSS JavaScript Node Express SQL MongoDB React
Continuation Courses AWS C# Java Python

WORK EXPERIENCE

US Cold Storage 2008-2010 Forklift Driver 2 years

Forklift Operator, Loaded and unloaded trucks both international and local shipments. Worked with inventory specialist to located missing product. Picked and put away loads off the main receiving dock.

Chilis Bar n Grill 2011-2017 Server-Cook 2 years - Manager 5 years
Service and Bar manager, ordered liquor and managed liquor and bar
inventory. Responsible for all hiring, training, scheduling, and disciplining for
all front of house staff. Handled guest complaints and owned the guest
experience in the dining room.

Red Robin 2017-Current KM 3 Years - General Manager 2 years General Manager, General Manager, Responsible for all aspects of the restaurant. This includes recruiting, training, scheduling and discipline of all team members and mangers. I manage all budgets and restaurant metrics for guest satisfaction. I oversee ordering, food quality, food safety, and team member safety. On a monthly and quarterly basis I create a full report detailing our successes and short comings with plans to adapt and correct for the next period or quarter.